let questions = [
	{
		numb: 1,
		question: "Which is the biggest continent in the world?",
		answer: "Asia",
		options: ["North America", "Asia", "Africa", "Australia"],
	},
	{
		numb: 2,
		question: "Which is longest river in the world?",
		answer: "Nile",
		options: ["Niger", "Great Ganga", "Amazon", "Nile"],
	},
	{
		numb: 3,
		question: "Which is the largest ocean in the world?",
		answer: "Pacific Ocean",
		options: [
			"Pacific Ocean",
			"Arctic Ocean",
			"Indian Ocean",
			"Atlantic Ocean",
		],
	},
	{
		numb: 4,
		question: "Which is India`s first super computer?",
		answer: "Param8000",
		options: ["param80000", "param800", "param8", "Param8000"],
	},
	{
		numb: 5,
		question: "Which bank is called bankers bank of India?",
		answer: "Reserve Bank of India",
		options: [
			"Reserve Bank of India",
			"Punjab National Bank",
			"ICICI Bank",
			"State Bank of India",
		],
	},
	{
		numb: 6,
		question: "Which is largest animal in the world?",
		answer: "Blue whale",
		options: ["Giraffe", "Blue whale", "Elephant", "Shark"],
	},
	{
		numb: 7,
		question: "Which is largest island in the world?",
		answer: "Greenland",
		options: ["Hawaii", "Andaman Nicobar", "Greenland", "New Guinea"],
	},
	{
		numb: 8,
		question: "Which is the 29th state of India?",
		answer: "Telangana",
		options: [
			"Uttar Pradesh",
			"Uttarakhand",
			"Telangana",
			"Madhya Pradesh",
		],
	},
	{
		numb: 9,
		question: "Which continent is known as Dark Continent?",
		answer: "Africa",
		options: ["Africa", "Asia", "Australia", "South America"],
	},
	{
		numb: 10,
		question: "Which is the highest dam of India?",
		answer: "Tehri Dam",
		options: [
			"Sardar Sarovar Dam",
			"Rihand Dam",
			"Tehri Dam",
			"Mettur Dam",
		],
	},
];
